Guide to the Abe Burrows papers, 1904-1993
The New York Public Library. Billy Rose Theatre Division.
- Series III: Production Files, 1912-1992; 588728; 54 boxes
  - Sub-series 2 - Not Produced, 1912-1981 and n.d; 589358; 5 boxes
    - Tango Mogador, book by Abe Burrows, music by John Kander, lyrics by Fred Ebb, based on original screenplay by Rod Amateau and Harold Nebenzal, 589419
      - Clippings, 1971 Oct 10; 589433; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Croque Monsieur by Marcel Mithois, 589434
      - Adapted script, n.d.; 589435; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1973; 589436; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Program for French production, 1965; 589437; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Jacobowsky, a musical by Stan Daniels, 589438
      - Script, mostly clean, n.d.; 589439; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Draft, partial, n.d.; 589440; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Notes, synopsis, list of scenes and draft pages, 589441; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Sheet music, 1968; 589442; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence on contracts, 1975; 589443; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1975; 589444; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Too Much Johnson by William Gillette, 589445
      - Published script (with undated revisions), 1912; 589446; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - Script with revisions and accompanying letter, 1975; 589447; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - Script with revisions, 1975; 589448; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous draft pages, n.d.; 589449; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Scene designs by Oliver Smith, n.d.; 589450; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Cast list and tentative production schedule, 589451; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence on contracts, 1975; 589452; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Sub-series 3 - Scripts sent to Burrows, 1951-1978 and n.d; 589453; 17 folders
    Scripts, outlines, treatments, etc., some with accompanying correspondence, were sent to Burrows for consideration.
    Scripts are arranged alphabetically by author.
    - A New Kind of Revue by Norman Bel Geddes, 1951 June 14; 589454; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 5)
      Proposal, not script.
    - The Day They Kidnapped the Pope by Joao Bethencourt, 1975 Oct 24; 589455; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 6)
      Script, photocopied, in English, includes letter to Burrows from Stan Hurwitz and playbill from Belgium production.
    - But It's a Lovely Hollywood by Billy Boylan, 1971 Jan 26; 589456; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 7)
      Includes letter to Burrows from Anna-Marie and Scott McKay and a photo.
    - Schweyk by Bertolt Brecht, n.d.; 589457; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 8)
      Carbon copy, in English, called rough translation.
    - An Evening with Alexander Graham Bell by Betty Comden and Adolph Green, 589458; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - The Village Blacksmith by E. Y. Harburg and Fred Saidy, 1972 Apr 27; 589459; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 10)
      Story outline, photocopied, with letter to Burrows from Joel Schenker.
    - Jolie by Alma Kessler, n.d.; 589460; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 11)
      Story outline for a musical comedy with photograph.
    - Untitled play by Harry Kurnitz, n.d.; 589461; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Hit the Deck by Robert Lissauer, 1978 Mar 13; 589462; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 13)
      Script with lyrics, includes letter from author to Burrows.
    - How to Make More Money Than Men by Shepherd Mead, 1978 Mar 9; 589463; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 14)
      Script with letter to Burrows from author.
    - That Man Twain by Shepherd Mead, n.d.; 589464; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 15)
      Idea for a musical.
    - The Fairy by Ferenc Molnar, n.d.; 589465; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 16)
      Script with pencil revisions and staging directions in red.
    - I Was Dancing by Edwin O'Connor, n.d.; 589466; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Bert by Phyllis Robinson, 1976 Mar 15; 589467; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 18)
      A treatment for a musical based on the life and work of Bert Lahr.
    - Story of Vaudeville and Nora Bayes by Joel Schenker, 1975 Dec 17; 589468; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 19)
      Proposal with letter to Burrows from author.
    - For De Second Term, author unknown, 589469; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence with Brandt & Brandt Dramatic Department about scripts sent to Burrows, 1958-1963; 589470; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Sub-series 4 - Professional show business work, 1939-1992; 589471; 3 boxes
    This sub-series includes contracts and correspondence for radio and television appearances, contracts, correspondence and financial reports with Beresford Productions and the William Morris Agency, correspondence and other papers on copyright assignments with the firm of Harold Orenstein, contracts, correspondence and royalty statements from record and other music companies, and a few papers on miscellaneous theatrical investments.
    - Duffy's Tavern contracts and pamphlet, 1943-1944; 589472; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 1)
      Contracts are between Abe Burrows and Paramount Pictures.
    - Contract between Burrows and Paramount Pictures, 1945 May 14; 589473; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence between Burrows and CBS, 1946-1959; 589474; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence between Burrows and Lambert and Feasley (Advertising) on his radio shows, 1947-1948; 589475; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence on Abe Burrows Almanac, a television show on CBS, 1949-1950; 589476; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 5)
      Includes photos of acts booked.
    - Correspondence and press release on CBS's We Take Your Word, 1950-1951; 589477; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence between Burrows and Goodson-Todman Productions, 1951-1977; 589478; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and contracts on Burrows' appearances on This Is Show Business, 1956; 589479; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence and contracts on Burrows' appearances on the Steve Allen Show, 1956-1958; 589480; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 9)
      Also includes script pages and clipping.
    - Correspondence and contracts on Burrows' appearances on the Jack Paar Show, 1959-1973; 589481; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence and contracts on Burrows' appearances on To Tell the Truth, 1961-1965; 589482; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Contracts with British and Canadian television, 1962-1963; 589483; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Employment agreement between Burrows and Beresford Productions, 1960-1970; 589484; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Contracts with Beresford Productions, 1955-1968; 589485; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence on Beresford Productions, 1955-1965; 589486; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence on Beresford Productions, 1966-1980; 589487; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Financial reports of Beresford Productions, 1962-1976; 589488; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Contracts with William Morris Agency, 1939; 589489; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Contracts and correspondence with William Morris Agency, 1945-1948; 589490; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Contracts and correspondence with William Morris Agency, 1949-1952; 589491; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Contracts and correspondence with William Morris Agency, 1953-1955; 589492; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Contracts and correspondence with William Morris Agency, 1956-1961; 589493; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Contracts and correspondence with William Morris Agency, 1962-1963; 589494; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Contracts and correspondence with William Morris Agency, 1964-1965; 589495; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Contracts and correspondence with William Morris Agency, 1966-1983; 589496; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence with William Morris Agency, 1984-1991; 589497; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Royalty payments from William Morris Agency, 1989-1992; 589498; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence and other papers on copyright, 1946-1987; 589499; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Orenstein files: copyright assignments, 1976-1992; 589500; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Orenstein files on copyright, 1980-1984; 589501; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Orenstein files on copyright, 1985-1991; 589502; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, contracts and royalty statements from Frank Music, 1943-1989; 589503; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, contracts and royalty statements from Decca Records, 1947-1969; 589504; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and royalty statements from Columbia Records, 1950-1959; 589505; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Carabe Music and AMSCAP: correspondence, contracts and copyright renewals, 1984-1986; 589506; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence between Carabe Music and Canadian Musical Reproduction Rights Agency, Ltd., 1984-1985; 589507; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Carabe Music and Henson Associates: correspondence and contracts, 1984-1987; 589508; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Theatrical investments: correspondence, lists and certificate, 1955-1957; 589509; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Burrows' pension statement from Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers and the League of New York, 1980 May 1; 589510; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Series IV: Radio Scripts, 1941-1965; 589511; 3 boxes and 27 volumes
  - Sub-series 1 - Unbound scripts, 1943-1965; 589512; 3 boxes
    These unbound radio scripts were not included in the run of bound scripts. Titles include Duffy's Tavern, Holiday and Company, The Ford Show, Abe Burrows Show, The Bing Crosby Show, Breakfast with Burrows, We Take Your Word, and the television show, Abe Burrows Alamanac.
    - Script with pencilled deletions and published pamphlet forDuffy's Tavern, 1943 Nov 23; 589513; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 1)
      This script is different from the Library's bound version. The pamphlet includes an article by Burrows on Ed Gardner.
    - Scripts for Holiday and Company, 1946 Jan 25-Apr 29; 589514; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 2)
      Scripts are different from Library's bound versions. Also one memo, 1950 May 19, against possible adaptation to television.
    - Script, mostly clean, for The Ford Show with Dinah Shore, 1947 Feb 26; 589515; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 3)
      Library's bound scripts are earlier.
    - Audition scripts for Abe Burrows Show, 1947; 589516; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Scripts with notations for Abe Burrows Show, 1947 Aug 30-Nov 29; 589517; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 5)
      Scripts have some variations from Library's bound versions.
    - Scripts with notations for Abe Burrows Show, 1947 Dec 6-1948 Feb 14; 589518; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Scripts with notations for Abe Burrows Show, 1948 Feb 21-May 8; 589519; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Scripts with notations for Abe Burrows Show, 1948 May 15-June 26; 589520; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Scripts with a few handwritten revisions for Bing Crosby Show, 1949; 589521; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Scripts, clean, for Breakfast with Burrows, 1949 July 11-Aug 8; 589522; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Scripts, clean, for Breakfast with Burrows, 1949 Aug 15-Sept 30; 589523; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Scripts, clean, for Breakfast with Burrows, 1949 Oct 7-28; 589524; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Scripts, carbons, for We Take Your Word, 1950 Jan 29-Apr 2; 589525; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Scripts, carbons, for We Take Your Word, 1950 Apr 9-July 11; 589526; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Scripts, carbons, for We Take Your Word, 1950 Sept 15-Dec 1; 589527; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Scripts, carbons, for We Take Your Word, 1950 Dec 8-1951 Feb 16; 589528; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Scripts, carbons, for We Take Your Word, 1951 Mar 2-Apr 30; 589529; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Scripts, carbons, for We Take Your Word, 1951 May 4-June 1 and n.d; 589530; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Television script for Abe Burrows Almanac, 1950 Feb 8; 589531; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous scripts and correspondence for radio and television appearances, 1949-1965 and n.d; 589532; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Sub-series 2 - Bound scripts, 1941-1950; 589533; 27 volumes
    These bound typed scripts include notes and revisions in pencil.
    - Duffy's Tavern, 1941 Mar 1-Sept 25; 589534; 1 volume (Volume 77)
    - Duffy's Tavern, 1941 Sept 16-Dec 17; 589535; 1 volume (Volume 78)
    - Duffy's Tavern, 1942 Jan 22-Mar 31; 589536; 1 volume (Box 79)
    - Duffy's Tavern, 1942 Apr 6-Jun 30; 589537; 1 volume (Volume 80)
    - Duffy's Tavern, 1942 Oct 6-Dec 22; 589538; 1 volume (Volume 81)
    - Duffy's Tavern, 1943 Jan 5-Feb 23; 589539; 1 volume (Volume 82)
    - Duffy's Tavern, 1943 Mar 2-Jun 8; 589540; 1 volume (Volume 83)
    - Duffy's Tavern, 1943 Oct 4-Dec 21; 589541; 1 volume (Volume 84)
    - Duffy's Tavern, 1944 Jan 4-Apr 25; 589542; 1 volume (Volume 85)
    - Duffy's Tavern, 1944 May 2-Jun 27; 589543; 1 volume (Volume 86)
    - Duffy's Tavern, 1944 Sept 15-Nov 1; 589544; 1 volume (Volume 87)
    - Duffy's Tavern, 1944 Nov 3-Dec 29; 589545; 1 volume (Volume 88)
    - Duffy's Tavern, 1945 Jan 3-Mar 16; 589546; 1 volume (Volume 89)
    - Duffy's Tavern, 1945 Mar 28-May 11; 589547; 1 volume (Volume 90)
    - Holiday and Company, 1946 Feb 1-Apr 26; 589548; 1 volume (Volume 91)
    - The Ford Show, 1946 Sept 18-1947 Jan 29; 589549; 1 volume (Volume 92)
    - Abe Burrows Show, 1947 Jul 8-Sept 27; 589550; 1 volume (Volume 93)
    - Abe Burrows Show, 1947 Oct 4-Dec 27; 589551; 1 volume (Volume 94)
    - Abe Burrows Show, 1948 Jan 3-Feb 28; 589552; 1 volume (Volume 95)
    - Abe Burrows Show, 1948 Mar 6-Apr 24; 589553; 1 volume (Volume 96)
    - Abe Burrows Show, 1948 May 1-June 26; 589554; 1 volume (Volume 97)
    - Breakfast with Burrows, 1949 Jun 27-Jul 25; 589555; 1 volume (Volume 98)
    - Breakfast with Burrows, 1949 Aug 1-15; 589556; 1 volume (Volume 99)
    - Breakfast with Burrows, 1949 Sept 9-30; 589557; 1 volume (Volume 100)
    - Breakfast with Burrows, 1949 Oct 7-28; 589558; 1 volume (Volume 101)
    - Abe Burrows Almanac on television Playhouse 51, 1950 Jan 4-25 and n.d; 589559; 1 volume (Volume 102)
    - Abe Burrows Almanac on televisionPlayhouse 51, 1950 Feb 1-Mar 29; 589560; 1 volume (Volume 103)
- Series V: Songs / Abe Burrows Songbook, 1944-1983; 589561; 1 box
  Series includes sheet music with notes, song title cards, drafts and notes for songs, correspondence, contracts, copyright assignments and royalty statements for songwriting, and notes, drafts, correspondence, copyright certificates, royalty statements, clippings and publicity for Burrows' book, Abe Burrows Songbook.
  - Published vocal score for Guys and Dolls, with Burrows' handwritten notes, 1953; 589562; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Sheet music, photocopied, of songs by Cole Porter, 1928-1929; 589563; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Handwritten sheet music, photocopied, of songs by Frank Loesser, 1967-1975; 589564; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 3)
    Includes typed notes by Loesser and Burrows and one published song, 1944.
  - Drafts and notes for songs, lists of titles and dates when composed, 1950?; 589565; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Song title cards, 3 x 5, 1947-1948; 589566; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Song title cards, 4 x 6, 1947-1950; 589567; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Song title cards, 5 x 8, 1947-1950; 589568; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence and contract on songwriting, 1947-1952; 589569; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Certificates of copyright registration, 1945 July 6; 589570; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Royalty statement from CBS Records, 1969 Apr 3; 589571; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Draft copy for Abe Burrows Songbook, 1955; 589572; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Notes for Abe Burrows Songbook, n.d.; 589573; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence about Abe Burrows Songbook, 1954-1962; 589574; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence and certificates on copyright renewal for Abe Burrows Songbook, 1980-1983; 589575; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Statement of royalties for Abe Burrows Songbook, 1955-1960; 589576; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - Publicity for Abe Burrows Songbook, 1955; 589577; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - Clippings for Abe Burrows Songbook, 1955-1956; 589578; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 17)
- Series VI: Writings, Sketches, Articles, Speeches by Abe Burrows, 1945-1982; 589579; 15 folders
  Includes notebooks and loose pages of writings consisting of sketches, notes and ideas for radio, television and movies, "bits", scripts, song lyrics, autobiographical materials and pages of an untitled novel; published articles by Burrows on both show business and non-show business topics; drafts of articles (unclear if ever published); notecards and drafts of speeches; a transcript of Burrows' remarks, What Can We Expect from Broadway? and some accompanying correspondence.
  - Song lyrics, sketches and lead-ins to songs, 589580; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 1)
    From black book 1.
  - Autobiographical writings and radio scripts, 1947-1948 and n.d; 589581; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 2)
    From black book 2.
  - Sketches and drafts, 1945-1954 and n.d; 589582; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Sketches for radio and television, 1947-1963 and n.d; 589583; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Sketches, notes and ideas for movies and television, 1953-1956 and n.d; 589584; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Sketches, bits and other writings, 589585; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Spiral notebook of writings, n.d.; 589586; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Pages of untitled novel, mostly handwritten, 1979; 589587; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Article by Burrows, The Making of Guys and Dolls, 1980 Jan; 589588; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 9)
    Article was published in The Atlantic Monthly.
  - Published articles (show business related) by Burrows, 1948-1969; 589589; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 10)
    Includes accompanying correspondence.
  - Published articles (not show related) by Burrows, 1950 -1979; 589590; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Drafts of articles by Burrows, not known if published, 1950-1976 and n.d; 589591; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Writer's World panel: What Can We Expect from Broadway?, 1966-1967; 589592; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 1)
    Includes transcript of Burrows' remarks.
  - Speeches in various drafts, 1962-1982 and n.d; 589593; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Notecards for speeches, 1967 and n.d; 589594; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 3)
- Series VII: Interviews and Articles about, 1957-1981; 589595; 5 folders
  This series consists of interviews with and articles about Burrows including Columbia University's oral history interview and E. J. Kahn's two-part article in The New Yorker magazine.
  - Transcript of Columbia University's oral history interview with Abe Burrows, 1959 Apr-June; 589596; 2 folders (Box 106, Folder 4-5)
    With accompanying letter.
  - Interview with Burrows for Contemporary Authors, 1980 Aug 4; 589597; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 6)
    Includes accompanying correspondence, 1980-1981
  - Miscellaneous interviews with Burrows, 1968-1976; 589598; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - E. J. Kahn's profile in The New Yorker on Burrows, 1957 May 11 & 18; 589599; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 8)
- Series VIII: Autobiography - Honest Abe, 1969-1982; 589600; 4.5 boxes
  The bulk of this series is various drafts of Burrows' autobiography. Also included are contracts, royalty statements, correspondence with editors, publishers, reviewers and fans, and clippings and publicity.
  - "Original manuscript,", n.d.; 589601; 3 folders (Box 106, Folder 9-11)
    Typescript with revisions and letter dated 1981 Feb 10. Chapters are as found (not in numerical order).
  - "Original manuscript,", n.d.; 589602; 3 folders (Box 107, Folder 1-3)
    Typescript with revisions, continuation of material in previous box. Chapters are as found (not in numerical order).
  - Carbon typescript, 1979 May 22; 589603; 4 folders (Box 107, Folder 4-7)
    Pages are in numerical order.
  - Typescript, mostly clean, 1979 July 9; 589604; 5 folders (Box 108, Folder 1-5)
    Chapters are in order.
  - Typescript, called "Early Stuff,", 1979 Dec 17; 589605; 2 folders (Box 108, Folder 6-7)
  - Typescript called "Early Stuff,", 1979 Dec 17; 589606; 2 folders (Box 109, Folder 1-2)
  - Typescript, partial draft, 1979 Mar-Sept; 589607; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Typescript drafts of sections, 1977 and n.d; 589608; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Loose draft pages, 1977-1979; 589609; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Loose draft pages, n.d.; 589610; 2 folders (Box 109, Folder 6-7)
  - Handwritten draft pages, 589611; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Spiral notebook with notes and drafts for memoirs, 589612; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Rough chapter titles, photo captions and song title lists, 1978-1979 and n.d; 589613; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Contracts and royalty statements, 1977-1982; 589614; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with editors and publishers, 1969-1980; 589615; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence with reviewers and fans, 1979-1980; 589616; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence and schedules for book promotion, 1980; 589617; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Clippings and publicity, 1979-1980; 589618; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 8)
- Series IX: Address books and calendars, 1968-1984; 589619; 2 boxes
  This series consists of two undated address books kept by Burrows and appointment calendars, mostly bound and used sporadically by Burrows in his later years.
  - Address book, n.d.; 589620; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Address book, n.d.; 589621; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Appointment calendar, 1968 or 1969; 589622; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Calendar, hardly used, just a few phone numbers, 1972; 589623; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Bound executive desk diary, 1976; 589624; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Bound executive desk diary, 1977; 589625; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Bound executive desk diary, 1979; 589626; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Bound executive desk diary, 1980; 589627; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Bound executive desk diary, 1981; 589628; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Bound executive desk diary, 1982; 589629; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Bound executive desk diary, 1983; 589630; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Bound executive desk diary, 1984; 589631; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 4)
- Series X: Personal Business Files, 1936-1990; 589632; 3 boxes
  This series contains correspondence, memos, contracts, financial statements and various reports relating to Burrows affairs outside the world of theater. With the exception of Sub-series 1. Legal papers which touches on both, most of this series relates to Burrows personal life, not his professional career.
  Organized in three sub-series: Sub-series 1: Legal papers; Sub-series 2: Financial papers; Sub-series 3: Miscellaneous personal papers on insurance, medical matters, taxes and homes.
  - Sub-series 1 - Legal, 1942-1990; 589633; 1 box